Preliminary Inventory of the John Dinges papers
Hoover Institution Archives
John Dinges papers
1968-1998
2005C46
Hoover Institution Archives
44 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (18 linear feet)
Writings, notes, correspondence, interview sound recordings and transcripts, trial transcripts, photocopies of government records, and printed matter, relating to General Manuel Noriega of Panama, his trial for drug trafficking, and American-Panamanian relations. Includes United States Department of State documents released in response to Freedom of Information Act requests. Used as research material for the book by John Dinges, Our Man in Panama: How General Noriega Used the United States and Made Millions in Drugs and Arms (New York, 1990).
Dinges, John, 1941-
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2005.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical/Historical Note
American journalist and author.
Scope and Content of Collection
Writings, notes, correspondence, interview sound recordings and transcripts, trial transcripts, photocopies of government records, and printed matter, relating to General Manuel Noriega of Panama, his trial for drug trafficking, and American-Panamanian relations. Includes United States Department of State documents released in response to Freedom of Information Act requests. Used as research material for the book by John Dinges, Our Man in Panama: How General Noriega Used the United States and Made Millions in Drugs and Arms (New York, 1990).
Noriega, Manuel Antonio, 1934-; United States. Dept. of State.; Drug traffic.; Panama--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Foreign relations--Panama.
- Notebooks, untitled (Box-folder 1: 1)
- Noriega (Box-folder 1: 2)
- Noriega #1- #5 (Box-folder 1: 3)
- Panama Update (Box-folder 1: 4)
- Address book (Box-folder 1: 5)
- Los Estados Unidos del Norte y los des-unidos del sur (Box-folder 1: 6)
- U.S. Senate. Drugs, Law Enforcement and Foreign Policy. Vol. 1, 2 (Box-folder 1: 7)
- Drugs/INAIR, Bilonick (Box-folder 2: 1)
- FOIA, Bush visit (Box-folder 2: 2)
- Brian Davidow/Saldarriaga/Krill (Box-folder 2: 3)
- Cesar Rodriguez/Krill (Box-folder 2: 4)
- Noriega trial, Residential, etc. (Box-folder 2: 5)
- Dexter Lehtinen (Box-folder 2: 6)
- Jon May (Box-folder 2: 7)
- Ramon Navarro (Box-folder 2: 8)
- Trial, Noriega in prison (Box-folder 2: 9)
- Noriega biography (Box-folder 2: 10)
- Noriega, CIA (Box-folder 2: 11)
- Castro connection (Box-folder 2: 12)
- Noriega (Box-folder 2: 13)
- Trial, codefendants (Box-folder 2: 14)
- Trial, Frank Rubino (Box-folder 2: 15)
- Clips, June-Sept. 1991, Panama (Box-folder 2: 16)
- Invasion, 50 kilos (Box-folder 2: 17)
- Boris Olarte (Box-folder 2: 18)
- Cesar Rodriguez (Box-folder 2: 19)
- NPR scripts (Box-folder 2: 20)
- Rubino memo, meeting at State (Box-folder 2: 21)
- Trial docs, Kalish letter (Box-folder 2: 22)
- Book update & notes (Box-folder 2: 23)
- Notes, Kerry hearings (Box-folder 2: 24)
- Ray Takiff (Box-folder 2: 25)
- Trial, general articles, Vanity Fair (Box-folder 3: 1)
- Clips, trial, Jan. 1990 (Box-folder 3: 2)
- Grenada call (Box-folder 3: 3)
- Trial, jury (Box-folder 3: 4)
- BCCI, First American (Box-folder 3: 5)
- Panama, Jose Blandon (Box-folder 3: 6)
- Felipe Camargo (Box-folder 3: 7)
- Carlton, Watson (Box-folder 3: 8)
- Trial, CIPA presentation (Box-folder 3: 9)
- Trial, clips, Feb.-June 1990 (Box-folder 3: 10)
- Trial, clips, July-Dec. 1990 (Box-folder 3: 11)
- Trial, Jan.-Mar. 1991 (Box-folder 3: 12)
- Trial, Apr.-June 1991 (Box-folder 3: 13)
- Trial, indictment (Box-folder 3: 14)
- Trial, experts/contacts (Box-folder 3: 15)
- Trial docs, CIPA ruling (Box-folder 3: 16)
- Trial, July-Aug. 1991 (Box-folder 3: 17)
- Trial, Sept. 1991 (Box-folder 3: 18)
- Trial, CIPA issues (Box-folder 3: 19)
- Trial, civil suit (Box-folder 3: 20)
- Trial docs, 404b/disclosure/public authority (Box-folder 3: 21)
- Trial docs, Noriega letter to Hoeveler (Box-folder 3: 22)
- Trial docs, CIA/Army payments (Box-folder 3: 23)
- JDC debriefs, Jan. 1990 (Box-folder 3: 24)
- Interview (various) (Box-folder 3: 25)
- FOIA, money laundering (Box-folder 3: 26)
- O'Keane (Box-folder 3: 27)
- Noriega docs, plane lease (Box-folder 4: 1)
- Noriega bio, Dillon, Oppenheimer (Box-folder 4: 2)
- Noriega, interviews (Box-folder 4: 3)
- Noriega, bio (Box-folder 4: 5)
- U.S. Senate. "Report on Panama,", 1987 (Box-folder 4: 6)
- Solis Palma, bio (Box-folder 4: 7)
- SouthCom, clips (Box-folder 4: 8)
- SouthCom (Box-folder 4: 9)
- SouthCom, Basiuk report (Box-folder 4: 10)
- SouthCom, T.F. 168.6 (Box-folder 4: 11)
- SouthCom, Galeta (Box-folder 4: 12)
- Soviet Union & Panama (Box-folder 4: 13)
- Carlton deposition (Box-folder 4: 14)
- Panama, politics (Box-folder 5: 1)
- El Malutino(?) pic (Box-folder 5: 2)
- Photos, out (Box-folder 5: 3)
- Photos (Box-folder 5: 4)
- Photos, in (Box-folder 5: 5)
- Lipthay(?) (Box-folder 5: 6)
- North & Noriega (Box-folder 5: 7)
- North notebooks #2 (Box-folder 5: 8)
- North & Noriega, trial stips (Box-folder 5: 9)
- North & Noriega, 4BC (Box-folder 5: 10)
- North, Walker (Box-folder 5: 11)
- North, McFarlane (Box-folder 5: 12)
- Oberlin talk (Box-folder 5: 13)
- Palmer, Michael (Box-folder 5: 14)
- Panama govt. response (Box-folder 5: 15)
- PRD (Box-folder 5: 16)
- Tongsun Park (Box-folder 5: 17)
- Pastora, La Penca (Box-folder 5: 18)
- Contra-Iran scandal (Box-folder 5: 19)
- PDF, CAA conference, 1988 (Box-folder 5: 20)
- PDF, promotions (Box-folder 5: 21)
- Paredes, Ruben Dario (Box-folder 5: 22)
- Iran/contra, the money (Box-folder 5: 23)
- Iran/contra & Panama (Box-folder 5: 24)
- Iran/contra, Hasenfus, Posada (Box-folder 5: 25)
- Noriega, Operaciones psicologicas (Box-folder 5: 26)
- Noriega, speeches (Box-folder 5: 27)
- Noriega, bio II (Box-folder 5: 28)
- Noriega, Hacia donde vas Panama? (Box-folder 5: 29)
- Noriega 1983 (Box-folder 5: 30)
- Noriega, letter of agreement/Plan Torrijos (Box-folder 5: 31)
- NSC doc, bogus (Box-folder 5: 32)
- Panama, June-Sept. 1989 (Box-folder 6: 1)
- Nov. 1989 (Box-folder 6: 2)
- Clips, Oct. 1989 (Box-folder 6: 3)
- Clips, op-ed (Box-folder 6: 4)
- Panama, FBIS, Mar.-Apr. 1990 (Box-folder 6: 5)
- Rogers, William (Box-folder 6: 6)
- Nestor Sanchez (Box-folder 6: 7)
- Nestor Sanchez, bio (Box-folder 6: 8)
- GAO, sanctions (Box-folder 6: 9)
- Sanctions (Box-folder 6: 10)
- Economy & sanctions, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 11)
- NYT index, 1968-1986 (Box-folder 6: 12)
- Luis Posada (Box-folder 6: 13)
- La Prensa (Box-folder 6: 14)
- Rabinowitz, Boudin (Box-folder 6: 15)
- Reimports (Box-folder 6: 16)
- Frontline pics (Box-folder 6: 17)
- Marea Pond (Box-folder 6: 18)
- Politics, 1989 elections (Box-folder 6: 19)
- Clips, Jan. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 1)
- Oct.-Dec. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 2)
- Clips, Panama, Jul 1988 (Box-folder 7: 3)
- Clips, Aug. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 4)
- Clips, Sept. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 5)
- Clips, May 1988 (Box-folder 7: 6)
- Clips, Jun 1988 (Box-folder 7: 7)
- Clips, Mar. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 8)
- Clips, Mar. 1988, select (Box-folder 7: 9)
- Clips, Apr. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 10)
- Clips, Apr. 1988 (Box-folder 7: 11)
- Clips, Jan.-Apr. 1989 (Box-folder 7: 12)
- Clips, Jan.-Feb. 1989 (Box-folder 7: 13)
- Clips, Feb. 1-13, 1988 (Box-folder 7: 14)
- Clips, Feb. 14-28, 1988 (Box-folder 7: 15)
- Clips, May 1989 (Box-folder 7: 16)
- LP, June-Dec. 1986 (Box-folder 8: 1)
- Pocas, 1985-86 (Box-folder 8: 2)
- Spanish, Jun-87 (Box-folder 8: 3)
- Clips, Jun 1987 (Box-folder 8: 4)
- Clips, Jan.-May 1987 (Box-folder 8: 5)
- Clips, 1986 (Box-folder 8: 6)
- Clips, Jul 1987 (Box-folder 8: 7)
- Clips, Feb. crisis, wire (Box-folder 8: 8)
- Clips, Nov.-Dec. 1987 (Box-folder 8: 9)
- Clips, Sept.-Oct. 1987 (Box-folder 8: 10)
- Clips, Aug. 1987 (Box-folder 8: 11)
- LP, 1984 (Box-folder 8: 12)
- Clips, 1984 (Box-folder 8: 13)
- Clips, 1983 (Box-folder 8: 14)
- LP clippings, 1983 (Box-folder 8: 15)
- FBIS, Aug.-Sept. 1983 (Box-folder 8: 16)
- Drugs, La Prensa, Pocas, 1983 (Box-folder 8: 17)
- LP, 1982 (Box-folder 8: 18)
- FBIS, Mar. 1982 (Box-folder 8: 19)
- Clips, 1981 (Box-folder 8: 20)
- Clips, 1982 (Box-folder 8: 21)
- Clips, 1980 (Box-folder 8: 22)
- Clips, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 8: 23)
- Seineldin (Box-folder 8: 24)
- Sound recordings (Box 9-10)
  Scope and Contents note
  Sound recordings on 104 compact sound cassettes and 1 sound microcasette.
  - McAuliffe (tape) (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Kellner (tape) (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Sayre (tape) (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Sanford/Lewis (tape) (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Lewis (tape) (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Herrera (tape) (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - Herrera (tape) (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Barlette(?) (tape) (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Arias Calderon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - Bly (tape) (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Bly (tape) (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 14)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Sanchez (tape) (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Ormsby/pilots (tape) (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Carlos Rodriguez (tape) (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Ragnoni(?) (sound microcassette) (Box-folder 9: 20)
  - Eden Pastora (tape) (Box-folder 9: 21)
  - Rio Hato/Porras (tape) (Box-folder 9: 22)
  - Jordan (tape) (Box-folder 9: 23)
  - Dot (?) (tape) (Box-folder 9: 24)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 9: 25)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 9: 26)
  - Barria (tape) (Box-folder 9: 27)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 9: 28)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 9: 29)
  - Dan M[illegible] (tape) (Box-folder 9: 30)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 9: 31)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 9: 32)
  - Carlos Lopez Guevara (tape) (Box-folder 9: 33)
  - Edo Herrera (tape) (Box-folder 9: 34)
  - DEA/Kennedy (tape) (Box-folder 9: 35)
  - Gregorie (tape) (Box-folder 9: 36)
  - Gregorie (tape) (Box-folder 9: 37)
  - Esquivel (tape) (Box-folder 9: 38)
  - Eisenman (tape) (Box-folder 9: 39)
  - Miranda (tape) (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - McGrath/Vallarina (tape) (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Lewis (tape) (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Lewis/Miranda (tape) (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Noriega (tape) (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Villalaz (tape) (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Demoss (tape) (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Demoss (tape) (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Demoss (tape) (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 14)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 15)
  - Villalaz (tape) (Box-folder 10: 16)
  - Moritz/Hull (tape) (Box-folder 10: 17)
  - Jordan (tape) (Box-folder 10: 18)
  - Grilli (tape) (Box-folder 10: 19)
  - Kellner (tape) (Box-folder 10: 20)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 21)
  - Eden P. (tape) (Box-folder 10: 22)
  - Rogers (tape) (Box-folder 10: 23)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 24)
  - Strickler (tape) (Box-folder 10: 25)
  - Spadafora (tape) (Box-folder 10: 26)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 27)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 28)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 29)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 10: 30)
  - Senate staff meeting (tape) (Box-folder 10: 31)
  - Senate staff (tape) (Box-folder 10: 32)
  - Owen (tape) (Box-folder 10: 33)
  - Rio Hato/Porras (tape) (Box-folder 10: 34)
  - PRD rally/Caldera (tape) (Box-folder 10: 35)
  - Andres O./Melo (tape) (Box-folder 10: 36)
  - Stone (tape) (Box-folder 10: 37)
  - DH (tape) (Box-folder 10: 38)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 11: 1)
- FBIS, 1985 (Box-folder 11: 2)
- LP, Jan.-Aug. 1985 (Box-folder 11: 3)
- LP, Jan.-May 1986 (Box-folder 11: 4)
- Clips, 1985 (Box-folder 11: 5)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 12: 1)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 13: 1)
- Renato Pereira, Panama fuerzas armadas y politica (Box-folder 14: 1)
- Mayin Correa, Dias de lucha y exilio (Box-folder 14: 2)
- En Pocas palabras (Box-folder 14: 3)
- Panama: Autodeterminacion versus intervencion de Estados Unidos (Box-folder 14: 4)
- William R. Hughes and Ivan A. Quintero, Quienes son los duenos de Panama? (Box-folder 14: 5)
- Medoro Lagos, Noriega: Legitima alternativa de la causa panamena (Box-folder 14: 6)
- Book drafts (Box-folder 14: 7)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 14: 8)
- Dinges appeals (Box-folder 14: 9)
- Foreign Policy (Summer 1990) (Box-folder 15: 1)
- Mayin Correa, La gran rebelion blanca (2 copies) (Box-folder 15: 2)
- Panama: Structural Change and Growth Prospects (Box-folder 15: 3)
- Special Warfare Area Handbook for Panama (Box-folder 15: 4)
- Philip M. Crane, Surrender in Panama (Box-folder 15: 5)
- Raul Arias de Para, Asi fue el fraude (Box-folder 15: 6)
- Computer disks (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Miguel Antonio Bernal, Militarismo y administracion de justicia (Box-folder 16: 2)
- Panama question (Box-folder 16: 3)
- John Dinges interrogatory (tape) (Box-folder 16: 4)
- The Use of Armed Force in International Affairs: The Case of Panama (2 copies) (Box-folder 16: 5)
- Miscellaneous letters, press releases, printed matter (Box-folder 16: 6)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 16: 7)
- Roberto Diaz Herrera, Panama: Mucho mas que Noriega (Box-folder 16: 8)
- Miguel Antonio Bernal V., Reformas o constituyente? (Box-folder 16: 9)
- Tareas (Oct.-Dec. 1987) (Box-folder 16: 10)
- Carlos Bolivar Pedreschi, De la proteccion del canal a la militarizacion del pais (Box-folder 16: 11)
- Drugs, International Security and U.S. Public Policy (Box-folder 16: 12)
- Jose Steinsleger, Panama en el ano del dragon (Box-folder 17: 1)
- Notebooks (Box-folder 17: 2)
- Miscellaneous notes and printed matter (Box-folder 17: 3)
- Panama speech (Box-folder 17: 4)
- Avirgan v. Hull, declaration of plaintiffs' counsel (Box-folder 17: 5)
- White Paper on the Panama Crisis (EIR, 2 copies) (Box-folder 17: 6)
- Human Rights in Panama (Box-folder 17: 7)
- Ambler H. Moss, Jr., "Panama's Crisis and United States Policy" (Box-folder 17: 8)
- Charlotte Elton et al., Canal: Desafio para los panamenos (Box-folder 17: 9)
- Miscellaneous letters, notes, press releases and printed matter (Box-folder 18: 1)
- Spadafora v. Noriega, complaint (Box-folder 18: 2)
- Panama today (Box-folder 18: 3)
- WOLA talk (Box-folder 18: 4)
- John Dinges, "Fact and Fiction about Noriega and Drugs" (Box-folder 18: 5)
- WOLA conference (Box-folder 18: 6)
- Book drafts (Box-folder 18: 7)
- Queries (Box-folder 18: 8)
- Noriega, U.S. propaganda (Box-folder 18: 9)
- Indictment (Box-folder 18: 10)
- LA response (Box-folder 18: 11)
- Dec. 1-19, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 12)
- Dec. 20, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 13)
- Dec. 20, 1989, briefings (Box-folder 18: 14)
- Dec. 21, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 15)
- Dec. 24, 1989 (Box-folder 18: 16)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 19: 1)
- Miscellaneous letters and printed matter (Box-folder 19: 2)
- LP/Pocas, 1984 (Box-folder 19: 3)
- Drugs, Gonzales/Costa Rica investigation (Box-folder 19: 4)
- Dick Gregorie (Box-folder 19: 5)
- Kennedy, DEA (Box-folder 19: 6)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 20: 1)
- Miscellaneous printed matter (Box-folder 20: 2)
- Notebooks, Panama, 1986, 1987, 1988 (Box-folder 20: 3)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 21: 1)
- Book drafts (Box-folder 22: 1)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 22: 2)
- Low Intensity Conflict Net (Box-folder 23: 1)
- Library of Congress (Box-folder 23: 2)
- Misc. Panama clips (Box-folder 23: 3)
- Cockburn, Frontline (Box-folder 23: 4)
- Debbie's notes (Box-folder 23: 5)
- Drugs, Nugan Hand (Box-folder 23: 6)
- Drugs, war on, military role (Box-folder 23: 7)
- Economy issues (Box-folder 23: 8)
- Panama bibliography (Box-folder 23: 9)
- Biblio, Spybase (Box-folder 23: 10)
- ARCA proposal (Box-folder 23: 11)
- CRS reports (Box-folder 23: 12)
- Christic suit (Box-folder 23: 13)
- Magazine articles (Box-folder 23: 14)
- Robert B. Anderson (Box-folder 23: 15)
- Bibliography (Box-folder 23: 16)
- Raul Arias de Para, "Anatomy of a Fraud" (Box-folder 23: 17)
- John Dinges, Our Man in Panama, photocopy (Box-folder 23: 18)
- Sound recordings
  On compact sound cassettes
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Illueca (tape) (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Davis (tape) (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Kozak (tape) (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - unlabeled tape (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Blandon (tape) (Box-folder 24: 15)
- Kerry report, contras, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 1)
- Leon Kellner (Box-folder 25: 2)
- Legal reading (Box-folder 25: 3)
- Lopez Guevara speech (Box-folder 25: 4)
- John Mann, thoughts (Box-folder 25: 5)
- Maps (Box-folder 25: 6)
- Marcos (Box-folder 25: 7)
- Merkle (Box-folder 25: 8)
- Interview, Anne Wrobleski, John Kerry (Box-folder 25: 9)
- Press conference, Galindo, Rogers, Sosa (Box-folder 25: 10)
- Press conference, Galindo & Sosa (Box-folder 25: 11)
- Press conference, Kerry, Kennedy, Helms (Box-folder 25: 12)
- Press conference, Sosa (Box-folder 25: 13)
- Kerry Committee (Box-folder 25: 14)
- Interview, D'Amato, Foley, Lott (Box-folder 25: 15)
- Interview, Juan Sosa (Box-folder 25: 16)
- Interview, Luis Moreno (Box-folder 25: 17)
- Interview, Dodd (Box-folder 25: 18)
- Interview, Delvalle (Box-folder 25: 19)
- Briefings, Feb.-Mar. 1988 (Box-folder 25: 20)
- Briefings, Apr. 1988 (Box-folder 25: 21)
- Interview, William Jordan (Box-folder 25: 22)
- Interview, Abrams (Box-folder 25: 23)
- Interview, Aquilino Boyd, Juan Sosa, Jorge Ritter (Box-folder 25: 24)
- Interview, D'Amato & Barry Slotnick (Box-folder 25: 25)
- Interview, Dodd & Robert Eisenmann (Box-folder 25: 26)
- Interview, Alfredo Garcia de Paredes (Box-folder 25: 27)
- Interview, Kerry (Box-folder 25: 28)
- Interview, Peter Kostmayer, Carlos Russel, Jaime Cobham, Peter Hakim (Box-folder 25: 29)
- Interview, Gabriel Lewis, Mario Rognon (Box-folder 25: 30)
- Interview, Juan Sosa & Alfonse D'Amato (Box-folder 25: 31)
- Musgrove, NSA (Box-folder 25: 32)
- NPR piece, script (Box-folder 25: 33)
- Script, Dinges, Feb. 1988 (Box-folder 25: 34)
- Script, CBC commentary (Box-folder 25: 35)
- Briefings, July 1988 (Box-folder 25: 36)
- Briefings, June 1988 (Box-folder 25: 37)
- Briefings, May 1988 (Box-folder 25: 38)
- Embassy, U.S. (Box-folder 26: 1)
- Experts on Panama (Box-folder 26: 2)
- Facts (Box-folder 26: 3)
- Henry Ford (Box-folder 26: 4)
- Foreign agents registration, Panama (Box-folder 26: 5)
- Paul Gorman (Box-folder 26: 6)
- Gallego, Hector (Box-folder 26: 7)
- Guns, Salvador crash (Box-folder 26: 8)
- Guns, Pastor book (Box-folder 26: 9)
- Guns, M-19 (Box-folder 26: 10)
- Pia Vesta, LP (Box-folder 26: 11)
- Guns, Pia Vesta (Box-folder 26: 12)
- Guns, arms traffic (Box-folder 26: 13)
- Guns, Villalaz charges (Box-folder 26: 14)
- Guns, Whitgreen case (Box-folder 26: 15)
- Guns, to Nicaragua (Box-folder 26: 16)
- Guns, Operation Black Eagle (Box-folder 26: 17)
- Guns, to contras (Box-folder 26: 18)
- Guns, to Sandinistas (Box-folder 26: 19)
- Harari, Michael (Box-folder 26: 20)
- Bill Hecht (Box-folder 26: 21)
- Helms role (Box-folder 26: 22)
- Eduardo Herrera Hassan (Box-folder 26: 23)
- Human rights (Box-folder 26: 24)
- Israel & Panama (Box-folder 26: 25)
- Israel, Hunter book (Box-folder 26: 26)
- Jackson & Noriega (Box-folder 26: 27)
- Kalish, bio (Box-folder 26: 28)
- Kalish, logs (Box-folder 26: 29)
- Drugs, Nexis (Box-folder 27: 1)
- Drugs, Melo, Cesar (Box-folder 27: 2)
- Drugs, Darien chron. (Box-folder 27: 3)
- Drugs, MH series (Box-folder 27: 4)
- Drugs, cartel meeting in Panama (Box-folder 27: 5)
- Drugs, cartel, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 6)
- Drugs, Medellin cartel (Box-folder 27: 7)
- Drugs, Barry Seal (Box-folder 27: 8)
- Drugs, Noriega revelations, 1986 (Box-folder 27: 9)
- Drugs, Noriega revelations, 1987 (Box-folder 27: 10)
- Drugs, Noriega revelations, 1988 (Box-folder 27: 11)
- Drugs, Samos (Box-folder 27: 12)
- Drugs, Georgia arrests (Box-folder 27: 13)
- Drugs, Gorriti (Box-folder 27: 14)
- Drugs, money/BCCI case (Box-folder 27: 15)
- BCCI (Box-folder 27: 16)
- Drugs, money laundering (Box-folder 27: 17)
- Drugs, price of cocaine (Box-folder 27: 18)
- Drugs, war on (Box-folder 27: 19)
- Drugs, Peru/Noriega (Box-folder 27: 20)
- Drugs, Royce series (Box-folder 27: 21)
- Drugs, William Spector (Box-folder 27: 22)
- Drug war, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 23)
- Economy, 1988 (Box-folder 27: 24)
- Economy (Box-folder 27: 25)
- P.R., Edelman (Box-folder 27: 26)
- Carlos Eleta (Box-folder 27: 27)
- Embassy of Panama, Sosa (Box-folder 27: 28)
- Chronologies, 1987 (Box-folder 28: 1)
- CIA, Jerry Svat et al. (Box-folder 28: 2)
- CIA, covert action (Box-folder 28: 3)
- CIA (Box-folder 28: 4)
- Civic crusade (Box-folder 28: 5)
- Colombia, 1985 (Box-folder 28: 6)
- Congress role, House (Box-folder 28: 7)
- Congress role, Senate (Box-folder 28: 8)
- Contadora (Box-folder 28: 9)
- Costa Rica investigation (Box-folder 28: 10)
- Cuba, Castro & Noriega (Box-folder 28: 11)
- Cuba, Ochoa arrest (Box-folder 28: 12)
- Cuba, U.S. report on covert action (Box-folder 28: 13)
- Alfonse D'Amato (Box-folder 28: 14)
- Arthur Davis, bio (Box-folder 28: 15)
- Delvalle, bio (Box-folder 28: 16)
- DEA, Jack Lawn (Box-folder 28: 17)
- Defeo report (Box-folder 28: 18)
- Drugs, DEA interview (Box-folder 28: 19)
- Drugs/CIA, inquiry (Box-folder 28: 20)
- DIA (Box-folder 28: 21)
- Diaz Herrera (Box-folder 28: 22)
- Drinan report, 1984 election (Box-folder 28: 23)
- Diaz Herrera, Spadafora (Box-folder 28: 24)
- Drugs/guns, ABC (Box-folder 28: 25)
- Drugs, contra link (Box-folder 28: 26)
- Drugs, Honduras, Bahamas (Box-folder 28: 27)
- Drug reports (Box-folder 28: 28)
- Drugs, Lehder (Box-folder 28: 29)
- Abrams, E. (Box-folder 29: 1)
- ADM, negotiations (Box-folder 29: 2)
- Adm. sanctions (Box-folder 29: 3)
- U.S. aid to Panama (Box-folder 29: 4)
- Rafael Alarcon (Box-folder 29: 5)
- Clips, analysis (Box-folder 29: 6)
- Articles, Rohter, Waas (Box-folder 29: 7)
- Articles, Rolling Stone, Village Voice (Box-folder 29: 8)
- Articles, American Lawyer (Box-folder 29: 9)
- Ricardo Arias (Box-folder 29: 10)
- Arnulfo Arias, bio. (Box-folder 29: 11)
- Bruce Bagley (Box-folder 29: 12)
- Barletta bio. (Box-folder 29: 13)
- Miguel Bernal (Box-folder 29: 14)
- Romulo Betancourt (Box-folder 29: 15)
- Bibliography (Box-folder 29: 16)
- Plan Blandon (Box-folder 29: 17)
- Briggs, bio. (Box-folder 29: 18)
- Silverio Brown (Box-folder 29: 19)
- Bush & Noriega (Box-folder 29: 20)
- Bush (Box-folder 29: 21)
- Bush & Noriega, singing sergeants (Box-folder 29: 22)
- Bush (Box-folder 29: 23)
- Businesses (Box-folder 29: 24)
- Panama Canal Treaty (Box-folder 29: 25)
- Canal, treaty docs (Box-folder 29: 26)
- Canal chronology (Box-folder 29: 27)
- Panama Canal Treaty (Box-folder 29: 28)
- Canal, Free Zone (Box-folder 29: 29)
- Clips, threat to canal (Box-folder 29: 30)
- Panama Canal (Box-folder 29: 31)
- Canal, P.R. (Box-folder 29: 32)
- Jack Carlton Reed, Carlos Lehder (Box-folder 29: 33)
- Poindexter meeting, charity (Box-folder 29: 34)
- Christic Institute deposition (Box-folder 29: 35)
- Chronology (Box-folder 29: 36)
- Tomas Cabral (Box-folder 30: 1)
- Bramble, Bly (Box-folder 30: 2)